What happened to the pub is
Irish business.
Shut your gypsy mouth
and listen to your
instructions.
Eamonn Duggan?
My son and my daughter were
taken from me when they were
very small.
We're planning an expansion.
I'm taking premises in London.
The Italian gangs and the Jewish
gangs have been at war in
London.
The Jews have had the worst of
it. They need allies.
We take the opportunity
to show our hand.
That arrived an hour ago.
There's no name on it,
but it comes from Camden Town.
Well done, Tommy.
Now you're at war with Sabini.
~ Ada Shelby? ~ No.
~ Your brother broke the rules.
Sabini.
My face is the last thing
you'll ever see on earth.
See if the bastard's still
alive.
♪ Please don't reproach me
♪ For, for how empty
♪ My life has become
♪ I don't know what really
happened
♪ I watched your disappointment